Infidelity in Suburbia is a thriller, tv movie film directed by David Winning.
With her husband away at work, and her son at school, Laura dreams of a
home-renovation project to supplant her restless days.
Elliott, her irresistibly hot private contractor, soon
fulfills her more forbidden dreams.
Elliott Graverston, played by Marcus Rosner.
Laura Halpern, played by Sarah Butler.
Mira, played by Miranda Frigon.
Greg Halpern, played by Peter Benson.
Bill, played by Jay Hindle.
Steve, played by Jason William Lee.
Sarah Butler (born 1984/1985) is an American actress.
She is best known for playing the role of Jennifer Hills in the
2010 to 2015 I Spit on Your Grave film series.
Her last appearance was the title character in the
2020 TV movie Woman on the Edge.
The tone is intense.